<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Snapeve</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_maps">Maps</string>
    <string name="title_user">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_notification">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <string name="notfication_channel_id">channel_id_x</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps_fragment">Map</string>
    <string name="me_fragment_title">You</string>
    <string name="grp_fragment_title">Group</string>


    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">welcome to snapeve, get the first news</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Attend events nearby or get latest updates on events in your campus</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">see an event?</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Post events you would like to tell others about</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Earn reputation \n &amp; get popular</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc"></string>

    <string name="slide_5_title">Or Be part of a group\n for more fun</string>
    <string name="slide_5_desc"></string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">Earn your rewards</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc"></string>

    <string name="play_again_desc">To see the welcome slider again, goto Settings -> apps -> welcome slider -> clear data</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="title_activity_signup_grp_join">Signup_grp_join</string>

    <string name="set_privilege_set_1">Read and Post</string>
    <string name="set_privilege_set_3">Read only</string>
    <string name="set_privilege_set_2">post and manage group members</string>
    <!--<string name="set_privilege_set_1">Set privilege - Read and Post</string>-->
    <!--<string name="set_privilege_set_3">Set privilege - Read only</string>-->
    <!--<string name="set_privilege_set_2">Set privilege\n-->
    <!-- - post and manage group members</string>-->
    <string name="at_the_rate_string">\@</string>
    <string name="notification_setting">Notification</string>
    <string name="notiofcation_summary">Notification ON/OFF</string>
    <string name="agree_and_continue">Tap \"I agree and continue\" to accept</string>
    <string name="user_consent_text_1">CONSENT \n\nThank you for agreeing to participate in our study. \n \n Before we start, we’d like for you to read the informed consent information below. Informed consent refers to the voluntary choice of an individual to participate in research based on an accurate and complete understanding of its purposes, procedures, risks, benefits, and alternatives.  The study will be conducted anonymously and voluntarily.   If you have any questions before completing this study, please contact the investigators, Ajinkya Gaurkar (Faculty Adviser: Dr. Shimei Pan || Email - shimei@umbc.edu) by 240-917-8687 ez55574@umbc.edu  \n\n Informed consent:\n\n You must be of 18 years or older to participate in this experiment. \n\nThe purpose of this study is to understand user behavior in community-based information sharing.\nYou will use an android mobile application to share campus events at UMBC.\n\n During the study, you will: \n\n  1.\tdownload a free mobile application developed by us from Google playstore (limited to android users). \n\n 2.\tparticipate our study using system-assigned user accounts. \n\n 3.\tuse the app to post a campus event, share the event with others and respond to an existing post (e.g., commenting and validating). \n\n 4.\tanswer a survey questionnaire to evaluate the usability of the application.\n\nThe study will last for 4 weeks, during which the app automatically records the usage of various design features such as the frequency of posting, commenting and validating \n\nThe risks involved in participating the study is minimal. Similar to participating in typical social media activities, you may receive a negative comment. It is not an issue, since receiving criticism is expected in social media if it is not inappropriate. There are no tangible benefits for completing the study. But you may receive virtual points/rewards from the app. You may also receive useful information about UMBC campus events. \n\n Participation is entirely voluntary; you may at any time withdraw from participation. \n\n  All data obtained will be anonymous. There is no way for us to find out who you are, and your data will not be shared with any other parties under any circumstance. \n\n This study has been reviewed and approved by the UMBC Institutional Review Board (IRB).  A representative of that Board, from the Office of Research Protections and Compliance, is available to discuss the review process or my rights as a research participant.  Contact information of the Office is (410) 455-2737 or compliance@umbc.edu. \n\n After reading the consent items, click \"Accept and continue\" to get started with the application. If you\'d like to leave the application at any time, just click \"Logout\" from settings menu.</string>





</resources>
